<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>
   <context id="windows_azure_project" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to create and configure a new Azure Deployment Project for deploying your Java applications, runtime and server to the Azure cloud.
  </description>
        <topic label="Creating a Hello World application..." href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=234493"/>
    </context>


   <context id="windows_azure_project_roles" >
        <description>
This dialog allows you to configure a Azure role.
       </description>
        <topic label="Miscellaneous Role Configuration Settings" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
   </context>

   <context id="windows_azure_project_project_property" >
        <description>
This dialog allows you to edit the properties of your Azure Deployment Project.
 		</description>
        <topic label="Creating a Hello World application..." href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=234493"/>
   </context>


   <context id="windows_azure_project_remote_access_property" >
        <description>
This dialog allows you to configure remote access for all the roles in your project at the same time.
  		</description>
        <topic label="Enabling Remote Access in Azure Using Eclipse" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235085"/>
   </context>


   <context id="new_certificate_dialog" >
        <description>
This dialog allows you to create a new self-signed X.509 certificate that you can use for testing purposes in scenarios involving encryption or digital signing. 

Two files will be generated: a certificate file with the public key only (*.CER), and a file containing both the private and the public key (*.PFX).
  		</description>
   </context>
   
     <context id="storage_account_dialog" >
        <description>
This dialog allows you to register an existing Azure storage account in the list of storage accounts known to Eclipse.
  		</description>
   </context>

 <context id="windows_azure_debug_config" >
  <description>
This dialog enables you to automatically create remote debug configurations for your applications deployed to Azure:

1. Select the project containing the Java code that you wish to debug

2. Specify the types of debug configurations to create (emulator and/or cloud)

If creating a cloud configuration, you need to upload your deployment to Azure first, to obtain the host address assigned to your deployment. Then enter it here.

When done, you will see the new debug configuration(s) created for your workspace under the “Remote Java Application” category.

<b>Note: </b>Encryption support for debugging connections is not enabled yet, therefore using remote debugging for applications deployed to the public cloud is discouraged.
 </description>
 <topic label="Debugging Azure Applications in Eclipse" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235086"/>
  </context>
  
   
   <context id="windows_azure_caching_page" >
  <description>
This dialog enables you to configure co-located caching on a Azure Role.
 </description>
 <topic label="Co-located caching in Azure" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=264792"/>
   </context>
   
    <context id="windows_azure_certificates_page" >
  <description>
This dialog enables you to manage your certificates.
 </description>
 <topic label="Certificates" href=""/>
   </context>
   
   <context id="windows_azure_cache_dialog" >
  <description>
This dialog enables you to configure a named cache.
 </description>
 <topic label="Co-located caching in Azure" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=264792"/>
   </context>
   
  <context id="windows_azure_debug_page" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to configure the selected Azure role to accept remote debugging connections for your Java application and to automatically create the relevant debug configurations for the emulator and the cloud.
 </description>
 <topic label="Debugging in Azure Using Eclipse" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235086"/>
  </context>
  
  <context id="windows_azure_endpoint_page" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to configure the fire wall and port routing settings for your deployment, by enabling specific service end points.
 </description>
 <topic label="Miscellaneous Role Configuration Settings" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
  </context>

  <context id="windows_azure_envvar_page" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to specify the environment variables that you want to be set at the time the startup task for the selected Azure role is executed.
 </description>
 <topic label="Configuration Settings and Environment Variables" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
  </context>

  <context id="windows_azure_localstorage_page" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to configure temporary named local storage resources of the desired size in the virtual machine where your application will be run, and to save their automatically determined directory paths in environment variables that will be available when this role's startup task is executed.
 </description>
 <topic label="Configuration Settings and Environment Variables" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
 </context>

  <context id="windows_azure_loadbalance_page" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to enable HTTP session affinity (“sticky sessions”) for this Azure role, for the selected input end point.
 </description>
 <topic label="Load Balancing (Session Affinity)" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235088"/>
  </context>
  
  <context id="windows_azure_ssl_offloading_page" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to enable SSL offloading (HTTPS) for your Azure cloud service.
 </description>
  </context>
  
  <context id="windows_azure_importexport_dialog" >
  <description>
This dialog enables you to describe how to import and deploy a component into the selected Azure role.
 </description>
 <topic label="Miscellaneous Role Configuration Settings" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
  </context>

   <context id="windows_azure_serverconfiguration_page" >
  <description>
This dialog enables you to specify the JDK, the server and the applications to include in your deployment.
 </description>
  <topic label="Miscellaneous Role Configuration Settings" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
  </context>

   <context id="windows_azure_components_page" >
  <description>
This dialog enables you to specify components to import into and deploy with your deployment, as well as command lines to run at startup.
 </description>
  <topic label="Miscellaneous Role Configuration Settings" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
  </context>

  <context id="windows_azure_addapp_dialog" >
  <description>
This dialog allows you to add a Java application to your server deployment.
 </description>
  <topic label="Miscellaneous Role Configuration Settings" href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=235087"/>
  </context>
  
  
  <context id="publish_project_command" title="Publish to Azure from Eclipse">
     <description>This dialog allows you to publish your deployment to the Azure cloud.
  </description>
  <topic label="Creating a Hello World Application..." href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=234493"/>  
  </context>
  
  
  <context id="new_hosted_service" title="Create a New Cloud Service">
    <description>This dialog allows you to create a new cloud service for your deployment.
	</description>
  </context>
  
  
  <context id="new_storage_account" title="Create a New Storage Account">
    <description>This dialog allows you to create a new storage account needed for uploading your deployment to the Azure cloud.
	</description>
  </context>
  
  
  <context id="unpublish_project_command" title="Unpublish a Deployment from Azure Cloud">
    <description>This dialog allows you to remove a previously published deployment from the Azure cloud.
	</description>
  </context>
  
  
  <context id="credentials_property_page" title="Credentials Configurations">
    <description>This dialog allows you to manage the credentials for your Azure subscriptions.
	</description>
  </context>
  
</contexts>
